[{"answer": "My life is -- is a bit crazy.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Has it a little bit of sex drugs and rock and roll?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "I didn't at all that I was going to be a star.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "I don't care what it takes?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "I mean, how do you create that kind of aura when by nature you're not really like that?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Well, definitely that, you know, beauty fades and who you are from within is forever.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What are the values do you think that she's instilled in you?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "I remember when we first had our single on the radio and I was starting to feel like I was hot.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "When does she -- since you became famous, successful, when has she been the most angry with you?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "EYONCE: No, absolutely.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "you've never sung again like that in a store with your mom?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I can say probably when I sang \"the last\" for the president.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "What is the moment for your mom?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Doesn't it sound amazing when you say things like that now?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I was 21.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "How old were you when that happened?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "It had a very deep effect on me.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "What effect did that have on you?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "I think he honestly had a spiritual awakening because he, you know -- and I don't want to paint him as this, you know, horrible man.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "So, when you had this time with him and he knew he was dying, do you think because he realized he wasn't going to be around this was the last chance to have that conversation with him?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I have two sisters from my father's first marriage, and he apologized to all of us, told us how much he loved us, which was a very emotional moment.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What did he say to you when he finally opened up?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "But do you dream, you know wishfully, of getting married, having more children --?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "That more conventional thing that your mother certainly dreamed of?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Young.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "But, what went wrong then?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Young, a lot going on.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Too young?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I think she would say that I'm extremely funny and goofy and the opposite of everything you said today about being cool and all that.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "If I was interviewing Zoe about you, how do you think she would describe you?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I am going to go to the Bahamas.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "How are you spending the Christmas holidays?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Do you do all that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "No, I know the tunes, but no.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Do you sing Christmas carols?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Goofy?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "If it's your sister, can you completely trust each other?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I don't know if I speak on behalf of Marie, but when we put the show together, you can throw as much money you want at a show.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "What's the thing that takes you to that level?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "We did.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Who of all the greats that have played in Vegas would you like to seen in the face of others?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "We worked with them.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "You saw them all?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Did you perform with Sinatra?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Sammy Davis?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Dean Martin?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "ORGAN: Elvis?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "They worked.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "What else made those guys?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Do you remember what Groucho Marx did now?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "He was the (inaudible).", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "-- which would have been illegal nowadays.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "So, this was completely inappropriate?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "John Wayne was a very stoic man.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "What was John Wayne like?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "OWNEY: I love America.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "How do you find America?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I think that we have lost our way a little bit.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Have we lost our way a bit, you think, globally?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I know who the boss is.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Who do you think is the boss?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Tell me about the project.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Listen, you know, behind every great man, there's a greater woman, right?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Well, we're spending Christmas with our kids.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "How are you spending Christmas?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Christmas turkey, yes.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Christmas turkey and all the trimmings?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "I love Brussels sprouts.", "docId": "111224pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Brussels sprouts?", "qSentId": 523}]